Hi Garrett, what was your initial
reaction to the trade given the the
success that you had with the Patriots?
>> Uh my initial reaction just goes to the
the logistics of like I got two young
girls. We got to figure out all right
that that's kind of honestly where my
where my thought goes. This is the
business we chose. This is the life we
chose. It's uh it's rewarding one. It's
a fun one, but this is part of it. Um,
yeah. And I think at the end of the day
in this league, you want want to be
where you wanted. And clearly Chicago
wanted me more than New England did
after last year. And and that's the way
the business goes. I'm uh my wife is
thrilled. This is where she was born.
This is where her father's from. It's
they live there. It's uh so it's
exciting. We're very excited now.
>> Where are they from in the the area?
>> Uh my wife was born in Neapville. That's
where they lived. So um spent some time
there when they were younger and then uh
moved to Charlotte, North Carolina.
Courtney,
sorry. Hey Garrett, how are you?
>> Good. Um,
>> walk us through, I guess, what February
was like. I mean, you just played for a
Super Bowl all these years into your
career. I mean, what was that experience
like for you?
>> Yeah, it was unbelievable. It's uh, you
can't put into words, you can't put a
price tag on it. It was uh, yeah, it was
it was the coolest moment of my career
for sure. Um,
leading up to it, winning all those
playoff games, it was just it felt like
a dream. And then, uh, kind of had to
hold myself. I was getting choked up
pregame like with the national anthem.
It was just, it was pretty emotional.
So, the game didn't go how we wanted to,
that's for sure. Uh, but a special year,
nonetheless. And yeah, and then you like
finish the game and finish the season
and then you're like, "Oh my gosh, it's
midFebruary." So, it's uh, certainly
never played that deep. Uh, but it was
an awesome experience. And I mean
throughout your career, you've played
with quarterbacks of a lot of different
experiences from Kirk now to Drake and
now you're gonna be playing with Caleb.
What is there one thing that you learned
from playing with a young quarterback
and the quarterback center exchange that
you think will translate now that you've
got another young quarterback in in
Caleb that you'll be playing with?
>> Maybe. I mean, everyone's different and
you try to not make comparisons uh in
this league, but I just I feel like
early in my career, I I learned
something from Kirk every day, whether
it was football related or life related.
And so that was just like a cool five
years for me to just kind of have a
mentor and a friend out there. And then
spent the year with Sam Darnold and we
were kind of the same experience at that
point and kind of learning from each
other. And then to the other end of the
spectrum with a 22-year-old quarterback
last year and and and Caleb is is the
same age. But um it's the same process
of like I want to get to know them and
they want to get to know me and and if
there's ways I can help them. I think I
think the quarterback position is so
unique that there's so many people
talking to them. There's so much on
their plate that you don't want to be a
guy that just adds to that. And so I
kind of want to pick my spots and find
ways. If I can help him in any way, then
great. That's what I'm here for. Um, but
I don't want to add I don't just want to
be another voice in their head. So,
>> Sean,
>> hey Garrett, welcome to uh Chicago. Just
wondering what sort of from afar just
watching Ben Johnson's offense, what
maybe caught your eye and what are kind
of your expectations uh going into to
working with Ben here?
>> Yeah, I'm I'm fired up. It's uh I'm not
just saying that playing against Ben
when I was in Minnesota and he was in
Detroit for all those years.
you watch certain offenses as an
offensive line and there's just there's
offenses that excite you and his is
certainly one of them. Um
it's you know what you're going to get.
You want to run the football and you
want to play action and and it's a
physical brand of football which I think
every lineman wants to sign up for. Um
and just the brief uh time I got to talk
with him that that he relayed that
message and so it's going to be
exciting. It's going to be a lot of hard
work and and and that's what I'm ready
to sign up for. Dan
>> Garrett, can you uh take us into the the
depths of your college relationship with
Joe Tuni and and being on the road with
Joe and now obviously reuniting with him
here?
>> Yeah, so spent two years with Joe in
college. Um
he's a stud. I mean, I think everyone in
college knew when he left college what
kind of player he was and and no one was
surprised by the success he's had. And
um it just it blows my mind that that
two teams have let that guy walk out of
the building. He's uh he's just a
special guy. He's a special he's a pro.
Like he handles everything the right
way. He's a good leader. He works his
butt off and he's consistent as they
come. Um and so I had some fun times
with him in college and and we've kind
of kept up over the years just obviously
being in the NFL together and playing
against him a few times, but uh
definitely excited to get back together
with him. Pat,
>> hey Garrett, uh what do you think you
learned about uh football uh during the
Super Bowl run and how can you share
that with a team that's got a lot of
inexperienced guys and not a lot of guys
who have been uh to that game or have
played a game at that level?
>> Learned about football. Such a that's a
tough one. Um,
you know, I I
don't know. It was it was a special
year. I think going in with they had
probably four wins the year before and
not a lot of expectations. I think I
think the team just worked. I think they
came together. They we worked hard and
um
you you got to have an identity in this
league as a team. How you play football,
how you go about your business. I see
that with the Bears and so you don't you
don't want to make comparisons. I think
comparisons are lame in this league, but
um it's just it all comes down to the
work. It's you got to have good OTAAS,
you got to have good training camp, and
you get into the season, you're
constantly trying to get better. Um and
so I'm excited about the vision that
that Coach Johnson has for this team and
and
you're not you don't make comparisons,
you don't make predictions, but you just
you show up and work. And so that's what
I'm looking forward to do. Hello.
>> Welcome, Garrett.
>> Um,
>> oh, you're welcome. Uh, so I'm gonna
throw you a little curve here. Uh, Caleb
uh loves to compare his offensive
lineman to Marvel Cinematic Universe
characters he called Drew Dolman Hulk.
Is there a character uh that you aspire
to be? And what is your assessment or
your thoughts about Caleb in in
comparison?
two questions. Um, I'm not going to
self-proclaim myself as a Marvel
character yet. I will let uh I'll
certainly let Caleb handle that. Um, but
yeah, I'll just I'll leave that that
question right there. Um, and then yeah,
I got to spend a little bit of time with
Caleb. I flew up uh on Sunday to kind of
finalize the trade, do the physicals and
all that. Um, got to spend some time
with him and and I've heard great things
about him and and just that reaffirmed
everything that I've heard. He's uh he's
an awesome awesome guy and he's
obviously an awesome player. So looking
forward to getting to work with him and
um helping him any way I can and
learning from him as well.
>> Adam,
>> uh hey Garrett, uh outside of Joe, do
you have any other connections with
players or staff uh on the Bears? And
then I'm also just curious coming back
to the NFC North, your familiarity with
the division, how much you think that'll
help you?
>> Yeah. Um, not a ton of familiar
familiarity. Uh, I played golf with Cole
Command a few times. Um, so I know Cole
and we trained out in Arizona together a
little bit. Um, but I think that's the
fun part of the NFL is I signed to a new
team last year and knew a handful of
people and then you finished the year
and you got a whole whole new locker
room full of friends. So, um, that's
what OTAAS and training camp are about
is building these relationships and, uh,
I think it helps you on Sundays. Um, and
then the next part, uh, definitely
excited to get back to the north. Um,
it's a storied division with a bunch of
awesome rivalries. Uh, it's, yeah, the
black and blue division. That's it's
played in it for six years and and I
don't know about advantage. I mean,
teams change, rosters change, but just
from a familiarity standpoint, it's uh,
it's going to be exciting to get back
into Soldier Field and Lambo and and
playing some of those games.
>> Dion.
>> Hi, Garrett. Welcome. Um, a lot of your
Patriots teammates talked about your
importance in getting not just the
offensive line going, but the whole
offense going as a whole. As you went to
a new team, what did you learn about
that process of bringing everybody
together, especially when you're working
with a young quarterback?
>> Yeah, I think I think every year is
different. I think
briefly speaking on last year, over half
the roster was new. When uh when I got
there, it was a new coaching staff. um
over 50% of the players were new. And so
you were trying to you're trying to
establish a culture. You're trying to
establish an identity. We had two
rookies on the left side. Um there was
only one returning starter on the O
line. And so that was more like all
right, we're starting at ground zero and
we're trying to build what this we want
this thing to be. And so that was a fun
process to be a part of. Um bringing
some old traditions that I had had and
Morgan Moses has had and just just a
different experience. Um, I think this
year is going to be different.
Obviously, um, it's not the first year
with this coaching staff. A lot of the
roster is similar. They have their
culture set. And so, I'm not coming in
to try and reestablish anything. I'm
just trying to learn from these guys.
How do you guys work? They won the
division last year. They had success. I
won a playoff game. Like, I'm not I'm
not coming in to try and change
anything. I'm coming in to help. And so,
that starts with building these
relationships and figuring out how I can
help. And then uh it just it goes from
there.
>> Last two. Dan
>> Garrett, you talked about your your
reaction to being traded. Where were you
physically when you got the news? And I
imagine that's probably uh blindsided a
little bit with the way it all unfolded.
>> Certainly. Certainly. Um yeah, it was a
wild 10 minutes. Uh uh we spend about a
month or two in Arizona for the
offseason. and I found a good gym here
with a with a bunch of O linemen that we
train together. And um we have two two
young little girls. Uh so my wife was
with them and I got a call um for the
Patriots and both those calls lasted
about a minute each and then it was
released to the public about a minute
later and then about a minute later I
got a call from Coach Johnson. So um
yeah, in a matter of about 10 minutes
everything changed and I hadn't had a
chance to even tell my wife. So that was
uh it was a shock to the system but uh I
think once you once you download it once
you process it um you start thinking
through the logistics and then you get
excited. So definitely shocked though.
>> Last one. Pat
>> Garrett. Was there a moment early last
year where you saw Drake May do
something and you went, "Oh, I think
this guy's ready for a leap or I think
he may be in for a special season."
>> No. The short answer is no. You know,
there's been seasons,
I tell people this all the time, there's
been seasons where I go into training
camp and I'm like, I don't really know
how good we're going to be. Um, you
just, you never know in this league.
That's why it's such a good league. And
so, you don't make, like I said, no
predictions and no comparisons. Like,
it's just it does you no good in this
league. And so, we Drake just went to
work every day. He was the same guy
every day. And, um, had an awesome year.
He's an awesome talent. And but no, I
don't think there's ever like a moment
you just see one play like he makes a
lot of good plays and a lot of people in
this league do. That's why we're all in
this league. Um so yeah, I think the
short answer is no. But uh I had an
awesome time with him for sure.
>> Awesome. Thanks so much, Garrett.
>> Yeah.